<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Examples on Rulehunter - Find simple rules in your data to meet your goals</title>
    <link>http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Examples on Rulehunter - Find simple rules in your data to meet your goals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Examples Included</title>
      <link>http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/examples_included/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/examples_included/</guid>
      <description>Included Experiments The examples/ directory of the repository contains a number of experiments, in examples/experiments/, to demonstrate how Rulehunter can be used:
acmeprinters_repair016_who_should_call_which_segment.yaml A call centre is representing a client that wants to offer a repair contract to customers who have bought printers from them in the past. The call centre needs to balance its need to make a profit with the needs of their client. This is used in a worked example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Processing the Examples</title>
      <link>http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/processing_the_examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/processing_the_examples/</guid>
      <description>Using the Examples The example experiments demonstrate well how Rulehunter works. Once you have run them you can tinker with them and compare the results.
Preparing the www Directory Before running rulehunter on the experiments you need to initialize the www directory.
For Linux/MacOS:
chmod +x examples/bin/init_www_unix.sh examples/bin/init_www_unix.sh  For Windows:
examples\bin\init_www_windows.bat  Processing the Experiments To process the experiments run rulehunter from the examples/ directory:
rulehunter  The website will be generated in the examples/www directory and can be viewed with a simple static webserver such as the following run from the examples/www directory:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Call Centre: Printer Repairs</title>
      <link>http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/call_centre_printer_repairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/call_centre_printer_repairs/</guid>
      <description>Outline A call centre is representing a client that wants to offer a repair contract to customers who have bought printers from them in the past. The call centre needs to balance its need to make a profit with the needs of their client.
The client&amp;rsquo;s requirements  The ROI (Return On Investment) must be at least 2.0 At least 25% of contacts must result in a repair contract They would like the total value of contracts to be as high as possible  The call centre&amp;rsquo;s requirements  The ROI for the call centre needs to be at least 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breast Cancer Diagnosis</title>
      <link>http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/breast_cancer_diagnosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rulehunter.com/docs/examples/breast_cancer_diagnosis/</guid>
      <description>Outline The following is a hypothetical scenario used purely to demonstrate Rulehunter. The results shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be used in any real-world setting.
A group of doctors want to find out what indicates that a patient is likely to have breast cancer. They want to reduce the chance that a patient with breast cancer is miss diagnosed and increase the speed with which letters are sent out for patients to have further investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>